<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web Application Vulnerabilities on Website Security</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/website-security/docs/vuln/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web Application Vulnerabilities on Website Security</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/website-security/docs/vuln/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Authentication, Session Management &amp; Data Exposure: Breaking into Web Applications and Finding Hidden Data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/website-security/docs/vuln/vuln/authentication-session-management-and-data-exposure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/website-security/docs/vuln/vuln/authentication-session-management-and-data-exposure/</guid>
      <description>Introduction linkThis tutorial explores common web application vulnerabilities related to authentication, session management, and data exposure. We&amp;rsquo;ll delve into techniques for breaking weak authentication mechanisms, exploiting session management flaws, identifying and accessing sensitive data, and exploring security misconfigurations using tools like Hydra, Burp Suite, and Nessus.&#xA;Broken Authentication and Session Management linkWeak Authentication:&#xA;Default or easily guessable credentials: Attackers can gain access using default usernames and passwords or by brute-forcing weak passwords.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Injection Attacks: Understanding and Exploiting XSS and SQLi with Burp Suite and sqlmap</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/website-security/docs/vuln/vuln/injection-attacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/website-security/docs/vuln/vuln/injection-attacks/</guid>
      <description>Introduction linkInjection attacks are a prevalent class of web application vulnerabilities that occur when untrusted data is sent to an interpreter as part of a command or query. This tutorial focuses on two common types of injection attacks: Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) and SQL Injection (SQLi). We&amp;rsquo;ll explore their mechanics, impact, and exploitation techniques using tools like Burp Suite and sqlmap.&#xA;Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) linkXSS vulnerabilities arise when user-supplied input is not properly sanitized and is reflected back to the browser.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
